[
  {
    "question": "In “Snow”, Charlie compares the Park’s attempts to preserve life to the ancient",
    "a": "Babylonians",
    "b": "Romans",
    "c": "Aztecs",
    "d": "Chinese",
    "e": "Egyptians",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "What do the two bars in the room at the Park say?",
    "a": "VIEW and DISCONNECT",
    "b": "ENTER and EXIT",
    "c": "START and STOP",
    "d": "REPLAY and PAUSE",
    "e": "ACCESS and RESET",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to “Snow”, what is Brownian movement?",
    "a": "the random paths of particles",
    "b": "the transfer of heat across conductors",
    "c": "the pathways of neurons in the brain",
    "d": "the conversion between states of matter",
    "e": "the orbits of objects around planets",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "In his first time visiting the Park, Charlie sees a memory of Georgie in",
    "a": "Paris",
    "b": "Bial",
    "c": "New York",
    "d": "London",
    "e": "Ibiza",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the first problem Charlie finds with the Park?",
    "a": "The order of memories is random.",
    "b": "The images do not show Georgie.",
    "c": "The memories are not real.",
    "d": "The images are low quality.",
    "e": "The memories cannot be stopped.",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the Director say is the cause of the problems with the Park?",
    "a": "the subjects of the recordings",
    "b": "the storage for the recordings",
    "c": "the construction of the building",
    "d": "the viewing system",
    "e": "the recording technology",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "In “Snow”, the title does NOT allude to",
    "a": "the place where Georgie died",
    "b": "a glass paperweight",
    "c": "memories from the winter",
    "d": "Georgie’s ashes after she dies",
    "e": "the grainy quality of the images over time",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Charlie claims Georgie married him for his",
    "a": "family",
    "b": "looks",
    "c": "job",
    "d": "property",
    "e": "money",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Park’s surveillance device takes the form of a",
    "a": "wasp",
    "b": "mosquito",
    "c": "hummingbird",
    "d": "parrot",
    "e": "butterfly",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "John Crawley FIRST wrote",
    "a": "poetry",
    "b": "screenplays",
    "c": "dramas",
    "d": "journalism",
    "e": "commercials",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Director in the end is revealed to be",
    "a": "dead",
    "b": "drunk",
    "c": "lost",
    "d": "depressed",
    "e": "scheming",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "“Snow” makes the argument that",
    "a": "technology cannot replace human memory",
    "b": "technology is invasive in our lives",
    "c": "life and death are equal to one another",
    "d": "memory lasts even after death",
    "e": "our technology will die with us",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Crawley’s attitude towards death in “Snow” is MOST similar to that in",
    "a": "Hawthorne’s “Rappaccini’s Daughter”",
    "b": "Butler’s “Childfinder”",
    "c": "Le Guin’s The Lathe of Heaven",
    "d": "Bierce’s “Moxon’s Master”",
    "e": "Bradbury’s “I Sing the Body Electric”",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which book did Crawley publish FIRST?",
    "a": "In Other Worlds",
    "b": "The Deep",
    "c": "Love & Sleep",
    "d": "Endless Things",
    "e": "Little Big",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who enrolled Georgie in the Park’s program?",
    "a": "Georgie’s son",
    "b": "Charlie’s parents",
    "c": "Georgie",
    "d": "Georgie’s first husband",
    "e": "Charlie",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Moore’s first published story was titled",
    "a": "“Nymph of Darkness”",
    "b": "“No Woman Born”",
    "c": "“Promised Land”",
    "d": "“Judgment Night”",
    "e": "“Shambleau”",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which adventurous protagonist did Moore include in several of her stories?",
    "a": "Juille",
    "b": "Northwest Smith",
    "c": "Deirdre",
    "d": "John Harris",
    "e": "Maltzer",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Moore launch her writing career?",
    "a": "writing editorials for a local newspaper",
    "b": "publishing in pulp magazines",
    "c": "writing television screenplays",
    "d": "joining her high school’s journalism club",
    "e": "publishing a collection of science fiction stories",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Moore’s husband was a(n)",
    "a": "chemistry professor",
    "b": "investigative reporter",
    "c": "television actor",
    "d": "science fiction writer",
    "e": "criminal lawyer",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following pseudonyms did Moore NOT use?",
    "a": "C. H. Liddell",
    "b": "Henry Kuttner",
    "c": "Keith Hammond",
    "d": "Lawrence O’Donnell",
    "e": "Lewis Padgett",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is Moore’s Jirel of Joiry series significant?",
    "a": "It established the trope of the infernal machine as a hallmark of modern science fiction.",
    "b": "It was the first book to include a female sword-and-sorcery hero.",
    "c": "It was the first work by a woman to be published in the pulp magazine Weird Tales.",
    "d": "It featured a groundbreaking representation of gender fluidity.",
    "e": "It received backlash for its controversial views on the Vietnam War.",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Moore wrote screenplays for the television series",
    "a": "77 Sunset Strip",
    "b": "The Outer Limits",
    "c": "Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea",
    "d": "Rod Brown of the Rocket Rangers",
    "e": "Operation Neptune",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 1963, Moore stopped writing after she",
    "a": "decided to pursue a master’s degree",
    "b": "lost her mother to cancer",
    "c": "suffered a miscarriage",
    "d": "was diagnosed with Alzheimer’s disease",
    "e": "married her second husband",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which children’s movie was based on one of Moore’s short stories?",
    "a": "Lost in Space",
    "b": "The Iron Giant",
    "c": "The Last Mimzy",
    "d": "Rim of the World",
    "e": "Flight of the Navigator",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "In “No Woman Born,” John Harris particularly remembers Deirdre for her",
    "a": "kindness",
    "b": "beauty",
    "c": "bravery",
    "d": "integrity",
    "e": "wit",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Deirdre die?",
    "a": "She was murdered.",
    "b": "She died in a car accident.",
    "c": "She suffered a heart attack.",
    "d": "She died in a fire.",
    "e": "She died from scarlet fever.",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Harris feel about Maltzer bringing Deirdre back to life?",
    "a": "He is frightened because he believes that Maltzer is playing God.",
    "b": "He is angry because he knows for certain that Deirdre would have preferred to be put to rest.",
    "c": "He feels permanently indebted to Maltzer for his kindness.",
    "d": "He is jealous of how much intimacy must now exist between Maltzer and Deirdre.",
    "e": "He is impressed by the precision Maltzer used to reconstruct Deirdre’s body.",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which scientist brings Deirdre back to life as a robot?",
    "a": "John Harris",
    "b": "Maltzer",
    "c": "Yarol",
    "d": "Jerry Foster",
    "e": "James Kelvin",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "The narrator compares Deirdre to the Biblical figure",
    "a": "Lazarus",
    "b": "Judas",
    "c": "Mary",
    "d": "Eve",
    "e": "David",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Deirdre say about her upcoming first performance?",
    "a": "She is unsure whether or not her new body can dance well.",
    "b": "She thinks performing will remind her of her painful death.",
    "c": "She is worried that the audience will be put off by her new appearance.",
    "d": "She is certain that the audience will enjoy her new talents.",
    "e": "She looks forward to being in the spotlight again.",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  }
]

